gleim.com 2019-02-04

# Privacy Policy - Gleim Exam Prep

Gleim Publications, Inc. and Gleim Internet, Inc. (“Gleim”) understand the importance of protecting your personal identifiable information. We respect your right to privacy and strive to gather only information that is necessary for providing you with the best services and products on the market. By submitting your information to Gleim, you are accepting the practices described here.

Gleim will ensure that the request of any personal information collected during the registration and purchasing processes will not be excessive. Gleim will not disclose any personal information identifying users to any third party without user consent unless required by law or otherwise needed in connection with legal proceedings.

Gleim may disclose navigational and transactional information in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics and demographics, but only in forms that do not reveal a user’s identity or confidential information. You may [opt-out of these statistics by using a browser add-on](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881).

Links to other websites may be provided by gleim.com. Please review each website’s privacy policy. In using such links, users should be aware that Gleim does not take responsibility for the privacy policies of, and usage of, personal information collected by other websites including, without limitation, those of any partner or affiliate.

Gleim uses “cookies,” which are short pieces of data that our server uses to identify and maintain your login information used in our online programs and services. This allows Gleim to enhance your experience at our website. These cookies do not contain any personal or private data.

Gleim may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy. Please e-mail any questions, comments, or concerns to [privacy@gleim.com](mailto:privacy@gleim.com).

## GleimTalk Privacy Policy

Gleim Conferencing, LLC (“ **Gleim** “) is committed to respecting the privacy of all persons using the Gleim website(s) (each, a “ **Site** “) and the GleimTalk conferencing service (the “ **Service** “). This Privacy Policy describes the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site and the Service.

In order to browse the public portions of a Site, you are not required to provide any personally identifiable information (although our websites and third-party software may collect some data and utilize cookies, see below). This Privacy Policy will apply to Gleim’s use of such information as you may provide (or that we may collect) through your use, viewing and access of the Site and/or the Service. The Service is designed to be an online conference service where users may interact with one another as if they were in the same room. Use of the Service is available only to users who have accepted Gleim’s Terms of Service (“ **Terms** “).

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on the Site and Service.

**Information We Collect**  
We may collect the following types of information:

**Information You Provide**  
Visitors to a Site are not required to disclose any personally identifiable information to browse the publicly available portions of a Site. Visitors to the Site may provide us with certain contact information if they wish to receive information from us, register to receive email updates or other news and to create a new account for use of the Service.

When you sign up for the Service, we ask you for some basic personal information. This includes personally identifying information such as your name, email address, username and a password that you create. Through use of the Service you may provide additional information for use and handling by Gleim in connection with the provision and maintenance of the Service, and you may also upload, submit or provide additional information by participating in Conferences.

**Video, Audio and Other Uploaded or Recorded Content for GleimTalk**  
When you use the Service to participate in a conference, meeting, seminar, discussion, presentation, virtual classroom or other event or interaction utilizing GleimTalk (any of the foregoing referred to as a “ **Conference** “), information provided by you is immediately transmitted to Gleim, the Conference moderator and the other participants in the Conference. In addition, some Conference moderators may be able to archive or store the Conferences for future display, transmission, use and/or viewing in the future by themselves, persons participating in the Conference and/or others. Gleim does not control who may be permitted access to Conferences; participation or access is determined by the moderator of the Conference. These Conferences, or portions thereof, may be available online for extended periods of time. Therefore, any information you upload, enter, submit or permit to be recorded (including without limitation, video or audio recording or streaming) when you participate in a Conference may be visible to and accessible to the Conference moderator, participants in the Conference and others to whom access is provided to such Conference or portions thereof.

Without limiting the above, you specifically acknowledge and understand that your username and any User Content will be publicly available and viewable by all participants in the Conference. You further acknowledge and agree that the Service includes a feature that allows for the Conference to be recorded. By joining a Conference you automatically consent to such recordings. If you do not consent to the recording, you should notify the other participants in the Conference and disable the recording feature. However, you understand that any participant in the Conference may enable such a recording feature at any time during the Conference with or without prior notice to or permission from you. You should not join or participate in any Conference if you do not agree to recording and we shall not be liable to you for any recording of the Conference as described herein or in our documentation. For further clarification, information exchanged using the “private chat” or similar features will be captured and recorded by Gleim and included in any text files for the Conference.

**Cookies**  
When you browse a Site or use the Service, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or device. We use cookies to improve the quality of the Sites and Service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results, and tracking user trends, such as how people use the Sites and Service.

**Automatically Collected Information; Log Information**  
When you visit a Site or access the Service via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with the Service, how long you visit a page, how many times you visit a page, information you search for, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account. When you use the Service using your smartphone or other mobile device, we collect information regarding device type, operating system, IP address and device ID. We do not share with third parties your personal information as linked with your IP address or device ID.

**User Communications**  
When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.

**How We Use and Share Information**

**Responding to Your Requests**  
If you have provided us information in connection with a request to receive information from us about the Service or any of our products or services or register for our mailing list, we will use your personally identified information to fulfill your requests and to send you such information or our newsletter. If you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter, you may do so by contacting us at support@gleimtalk.com.

**Administering the Service**  
We use information you provide and information we automatically collect to administer the Service, to allow you and other users to use the Service, and, if applicable, to process your payments. We will also analyze your information and use of the Service in order to improve and customize your experience, including remembering information so you will not have to reenter it, and provide access to your data or to provide access to recorded Conferences to which you have rights. We may also use such information to contact you regarding Service changes, system maintenance and outage issues, or account issues, or otherwise troubleshoot problems.

**Service Providers**  
We will disclose information to our service providers that work on our behalf or with us to fulfill your information requests and to provide the Service. We do not permit these providers to use your information other than as necessary to provide the services to us.

**Other Disclosures**  
We may disclose your information, including recordings or Conference content, if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or other governmental or law enforcement request, (b) enforce our Terms of Service including investigation of potential violations, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (d) assist in investigating any unauthorized use of the Service or (e) protect against or mitigate harm to the rights, property or safety of Gleim, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

**With Permission**  
If we use your personal information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected or other than as disclosed in this policy, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

**Aggregate and Non-personally Identifiable Information**  
We may also use non-personally identifiable information (including such as may be aggregated with information of other users so as to no longer be personally identifiable to any particular user) to analyze use of our Site and Service.

Except as set forth herein, we will not provide your personally identifiable information to any such unaffiliated parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent.

**Data Retention**  
Even after you delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed by other participants in a Conference, or it was copied or stored by other users. You may not have the authority or ability to remove information (including video, audio or other information) you submitted by participating in a Conference, which may be left on the Service for later viewing as determined by the Conference moderator for that event.

**Corporate Events**  
If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, your information may be included in the assets sold or transferred to the acquirer. You hereby agree that we may transfer or assign the information we have collected from you in connection with any such event. In the event of a bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used.

**Information Security**  
We will take reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. However, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or that unauthorized persons will not access or use your personal information for improper purposes. In the event of a breach of security affecting personal information or data on our servers, we will take such notification and other steps as may be required under applicable law.

**Accessing and Updating Personal Information**  
You may update, change or correct your basic account personal information through the Service. We will update your account and information as requested, provided that we may decline to update information if we determine it to be impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on recorded Conferences, backup tapes or other historical data). In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

**Disclosures**

Social Media Sites

We may have pages or other presence on various social networking sites or services, such as Facebook, Twitter and the like. Any information you post or provide through such sites and services will be subject to the policies of those sites and services.

Links

The Site or Service may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Gleim Site or Service. We do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our practices and policies. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other website before submitting your personal information. If any content provided by other users and participants in a Conference include any reference or links to a third-party website, you understand and agree that Gleim makes no representation regarding such websites or their products, services or privacy policies or practices.

Location of Servers

Our servers are located in the United States of America. If you are accessing the Site and Service from outside the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site or Service, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer and the maintenance and processing of such information in the United States.

Information of Children

This GleimTalk Site is not intended for use by minors under the age of thirteen (13). If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without verifiable parental consent, we will promptly take reasonable and appropriate actions to remove such user and delete any personal information from our servers.

Tracking

We do not track or collect personal data about your online activities once you leave the Site or Service.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: support@gleimtalk.com.

EFFECTIVE DATE: July 9, 2015
